always wanted to know more about basics
of infantry management then this course
of basics of infantry management will
help you
what will i discuss in this course the
impact of infantry on the supply chain i
will look at the types of infantry some
safety stock concepts and demand and
fluctuations and how to deal with those
the second part i will look at
optimizing our infantry levels looking
at other point techniques dealing with
uncertainty giving some insights in
economic order quantity and using the
max techniques
and last but not least i will introduce
some of the stock counting procedures so
please take a look at scm dojo community
and take other courses i posted over
there
you